johnsonville.com 2019-01-02

# Our Privacy Policy - Johnsonville.com

**You are a valued consumer at Johnsonville.com. Please take a moment to read how we protect, collect and use the information you provide through our websites and social media sites.**

### Modifications

We may, at our sole discretion, revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the Privacy Policy will be made available to you on the website. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you on the website prior to the effective date of the changes. By continuing to access or use this website after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the revised Privacy Policy, do not access this website.

### Your Privacy and Security at Johnsonville.com

Each visitor to Johnsonville.com is important to us. The security of your information is a top priority.

At Johnsonville, we always use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and storing consumer data. We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information.

### Collecting Information

Johnsonville only collects personal information that is willingly provided, and then, only to provide our customers with the best possible product and experience. If you choose to sign up for newsletter or the Enthusiast Club, we will collect your name, email address, mailing address and your social media information if you choose to sign up using your social media account. If you choose to make a purchase on our online store, Swagville, your payment information will be collected by our third party credit card processor, Authorize.net, in order to complete your payment. We never share your personal information or use it for purposes other than what it was originally given to us and with those third party providers that are required to complete your purchase. We do believe you have a right to know about information that we collect, and how we use it.

### Cookies

Like most web sites, Johnsonville.com uses cookies to improve your experience and provide a better service. 

A "cookie" is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive, containing information about the user, such as which pages of the site you visit or which products or recipes you click on for more information. We use cookies on our site, but none of them contain any information that could actually identify you as a person. Rather, cookies can help us provide you with information targeted to your interests. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session.

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can disable this function so that your browser will not accept cookies. Please be aware that disabling this function may impact your use and enjoyment of this website. If you choose to disable cookies on your browser, you will not be able to interact with the Enthusiast Club.

### IP Addresses

If you choose to submit an entry for a promotion we will collect your IP address for administrative purposes. IP addresses are not used to track a user’s session. This information only helps us determine how often different areas of our site are visited. We do not link IP address to any information that is personally identifiable.

### Website Analytics

Like many websites, our website uses Google Analytics to collect information about your use of our website. This information consists of information that your web browser automatically sends to Google, such as the web address of the page that you visit and your IP address. Google may also set cookies or read preexisting cookies. This information is stored on Google´s servers. Google uses this information to provide use with reports about traffic to our website and your visit to our website (such as the domain from which you access the internet, the web address of the website from which you linked to our site, the time and date of your visit the web pages that you view and click through). We will use this data to improve our website structure and content.

Google may also use this data in accordance with their Privacy Policy, which can be found at <http://www.google.com/privacy.html>. **For more detailed information on how Google uses your data through our Site, please visit<http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/>.**

### E-mail Newsletters 

Johnsonville.com allows you to receive e-mails about our latest recipes, products, events and promotions. You may elect to join our e-mail list when visiting our website, or we may automatically add you to that list when you use certain online features, such as signing up to participate in one of our online sweepstakes promotions through the Johnsonville.com website or through third party social media sites such as Facebook or Twitter. We may also ask you to identify departments or areas of specific interest to you, so we may better tailor our e-mails to match your preferences.

If you choose to receive e-mails from us, we will share your email information with our third party e-mail provider only for the purposes of sending those e-mails. 

Each e-mail you receive from Johnsonville will offer you the opportunity to cancel or "opt-out" of the Johnsonville Enthusiast Club e-mail list. If you don't like the idea of hearing from us via Johnsonville Enthusiast Club e-mails, please let us know by contacting us at 1-888-556-2728, or go to Johnsonville.com and click on the “Contact Johnsonville” section of the home page. Please provide us with your exact name and address, and we'll be sure to remove your information as soon as possible.

### Social Media Interaction

Johnsonville uses third party social media sites such as Facebook and Twitter to provide you with a more useful and entertaining experience with our events, promotions and products. This feature may require us to implement cookies and/or APIs provided by such social media platform to facilitate the communication. By interacting with Johnsonville through these third party social media sites, you are giving us permission to use the information you share with us. We cannot control any policies or terms of such third party platform. As a result, we cannot be responsible for any use of your information or content by a third party platform. 

This information will only be used in a way to improve our service and communication to you. We may use this data to provide you with information and experiences that better fit your preferences, or we may reply to you directly through these social media sites. 

### Children's Policy

Johnsonville recognizes the privacy interests of children and we encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests. No personally identifiable information is collected by Johnsonville from children under the age of 13 and this site is not intended for children under the age of 13.

If someone under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, Johnsonville asks that the parent or guardian of that person contact us at the e-mail address at the top of this Policy and request removal of the information from our records. Upon receiving your request, we will promptly remove such information from our records.

### Do Not Track

We will automatically collect cookies and other non-personally identifying information when you visit this site. Due to this automatic collection, we do not currently honor “do not track” requests. We do not currently participate in any third party ad networks, but we do use third party cookies as discussed above to track your visits across websites.

### Terms & Conditions for Personal and Non-commercial Use

This website is operated on behalf of Johnsonville, LLC, for your personal entertainment, information, education and communication. Please feel free to browse the site. You may download material on the site only for personal, non-commercial use, and you must retain all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the materials. You may not distribute, modify, transmit, reuse, re-post or use the content of the site, including the text, images, audio or video, for public or commercial purposes, without Johnsonville’s prior written permission.

### Postings

Johnsonville is under no obligation to monitor any posting or transmission to or about the site and assumes no responsibility or liability arising from the content of any such posting or transmission, nor for any error, defamation, libel, slander, omission, falsehood, obscenity, pornography, profanity, danger or inaccuracy contained therein or related thereto.  

You are prohibited from posting or transmitting any unlawful, threatening, libelous, defamatory, obscene, scandalous, inflammatory, pornographic or profane material, or any material that could constitute or encourage conduct that would be considered a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability or otherwise violate any law. Johnsonville will fully cooperate with any law enforcement authorities or court order requesting or directing Johnsonville to disclose the identity of anyone posting any such information or materials.

### Links

This website may contain links to unaffiliated third party websites. We have no responsibility or liability for such third party websites and do not endorse the same. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not share your personal information with them, and are not responsible for their privacy practices. We suggest you read the privacy policies on all third party applications, websites or services that you visit or use.

### In Summary

Johnsonville may terminate, change, suspend or discontinue any aspect of this site, including the availability of any features of the site, at any time and without notice. Johnsonville also reserves the right to block or deny access to the site to anyone, at any time, for any reason. 

### Contacting Johnsonville

This is the web site of Johnsonville, LLC.

Our postal address is  
**_P.O. Box 906  
__Sheboygan Falls, WI 53085_** _  
_  
We can be reached by telephone at **_1-888-556-BRAT (2728)_.**
